Adolfo Gonzalez

San Jacinto, CA

agonzalez45@ucmerced.edu http://adolfogonzalez.weebly.com

Software Engineer

Summary

I am a Software Developer with a passion for web automation. I have experience in designing and implementing software from end to end. I have multiple years of back end and front end technologies with a proficiency in Python, C++, SQL, and JavaScript.

Experience

Empowr (Social Crypto Platform)

Software Engineer San Diego, CA

Mar 2018-Present

- Implemented cryptocurrency payment API, which resulted in a 15% increase in revenues.
- Developed a user education page and raised user activity by 20%
- Designed front end and back end of a presentation platform to help users understand the current platform.

Interstate Steel Structures

Software Engineer

Riverside, CA

Feb 2018-Mar 2018

- Worked with the design engineering team to develop and create consumer facing applications for steel structures.
- Designed and Implemented the current full working website with SEO and has increased web traffic by 100%.
- Worked with stakeholders to understand the analytics objectives and needs to develop appropriate strategies for analytical tools and pricing tools.

The Wine Group

IT Operations Specialist

Tracy, Ca

May 2017-Feb 2018

- Acted as escalation point for client services and consistently resolved issues to internal and external workers.
- Administrated infrastructure: firewalls, database, malware and other processes.
- Built an internal technical documentation and manual for IT policies.

Projects Swift Chat

- Developed a chat application that allows random users to chat with each other in private and distributed rooms. Chooses users random and has complete anonymity.
- **Live Demo:** https://chat5server.herokuapp.com/
- Stack: Node, JavaScript, Socket.IO, Heroku, Express

Cryptocurrency Blockchain

- Developed a python blockchain that sends signed signs transactions using blockchain into a wallet.
- Skills: Python, Git

Web Automation Software

- Developed a Mac and Windows application that scrapes data from websites to process tasks for quick transactions.
- Skills: Python, JavaScript, HTML, Electron, Angular, Express

Extracurricular

Streetwear Innovation

Creator – Software Developer and Marketing Analyst

- Developed and sold 100+ copies of Mac software for web automation.
- Increased social media engagement by 400%. From 20 to over 500 and increasing followers.

IBM

Software Engineer – Mainframe Programmer

- Acquired certification for mainframe programming from IBM.
- Developed and Debugged mainframe applications using COBOL, JCL and CICS

Skills & Languages

Back End: Python, C++, C#, Java, Node, REST, SQL **Front end:** Asp .Net, JavaScript, React, HTML/CSS

Other: Git, Android Studio, Heroku

Education University of California, Merced

Graduated in May 2017

B.S. in Computer Science and Engineering